Hello Kay, hello Ian, hello Pauline
Nice to see you, lovely smile by the way
Thank you
Radiant
What do you do, Pauline?
I look after the personnel within the planning and leisure departments of Dudley Council
- Oh, Dudley?
- Yes
- I love Dudley
Er, I used to worry about my health, you know?
But that was back when I had some
[LAUGHTER]
What other jobs have you done, Pauline, before you took up what you do?
I've worked as a clerical assistant for a firm of solicitors
I've worked in a shop
And I've worked at a holiday camp as a chalet maid
- Oh really?
- Yes
- Oh yeah! Any funny incidents on a holiday camp?
Yes, we had one particular day when I was setting off with my bucket and mop and bits and pieces
and a gorilla picked me up, threw me over his shoulders and ran `round the camp with me and all my truntlements
I remember you now
[LAUGHTER]
- Ian, you're a social worker, Sir?
- I am, yes
And what do you do in Wakefield?
I carry out community care assessments on adults with learning disabilities
Oh right! Er, how did you come to meet your wife?
Well, about thirty years ago
The day I started in social work
We shared a desk and a phone
And it was hate at first sight
[LAUGHTER]
Same with me and my first wife
I met her at a drunken orgy and I found her so annoying
For one thing she was supposed to be home taking care of the kids
[LAUGHTER]
If you...
If you were not a social worker, Ian, what would be your dream job?
I'd like to be a driver of a steam locomotive
- Oh you're a kiddy at heart?
- I am
- Never grown up?
- No
Actually I can understand that because when you were a kiddy
working for the railways was a very, very nice job
But there's no loyalty to old employees any more:
Three years as an engine driver and my cousin got sacked just because
he didn't slow down and stop at one station!
Admittedly: Euston
[LAUGHTER]
Kay? You sell stuff?
I sell stuff, yes, I sell metal boxes
- Little boxes?
- No, metal boxes
- Metal boxes, yes
What form do they take, little secure containers?
Some. Well, all sizes really from that size to wardrobes.
- Anything you can lock up?
- Yes
- Yeah
We make cabinets for electricity companies
- Ah, right, meters?
- Meter cabinets
- Hate meters
I've hated meters ever since I was a little boy because my dad painted ours red and told me it was my money box
[LAUGHTER]
Before you started making, selling tin boxes, metal boxes, (steel boxes?), what did you do?
- I worked for a wallpaper company
- Oh, yeah? Any funny customers?
- We had a few funny customers, yes:
One in particular rang up to complain that there were faces in her wallpaper which... [LAUGHTER]
What, lumpy ones? She was just getting visions was she?
She was having visions. We sent someone out to investigate.
I think people often see imaginary faces that aren't there, don't they?
In clouds, in coal fires...
The stalls of theatres where I'm appearing?
[LAUGHTER]
What about other jobs, Kay, what else have you done?
I've had several. I worked for a time-share company in the far north of Scotland for a short time.
Oh, really, far north? Oh yeah, I had a girlfriend up in the far north.
Well, she was very popular
She was the favourite of all the lads between the Orkneys and the Shetlands
In fact she was the original Fair Isle Pushover
[LAUGHTER]
And what about your partner's job, what does your...?
- He's an aspiring author
- Oh, really?
- Not published yet
- But he is writing
- He's hoping. He's writing.
- Money in mysteries writing..
Get him to write some mysteries because they sell, they really do
Do you know how many mystery writers it takes to change a light bulb?
Only one. But it needs a very clever twist at the end.
[LAUGHTER]
Would you please make my guests feel welcome, ladies and gentlemen?
Thank you
[APPLAUSE]
Ha Ha. Lovely.
Lovely story